

How to reach me:

My Website:

Softwarepower.ir



Email:

ahmad.vakil.safir@gmail.com



l inkedin

linkedin.com/in/ahmadrezavakila



Github:

GitHub AhmadVakil



Cell:

+98 904 610 9204



I Can Speak:

English (IELTS 7 - Valid TRF) Swedish (Working proficiency) Farsi (Mother tongue)

Personal Profile

I am a self-driven
software and system
developer with
proficient programming
and problem solving
skills. I am a team
player with significant
work experience in
Swedish and
international companies
with relevant academic
background.

Educational Training

Linnéuniversitetet - Växjö, Sweden 2015 - 2018

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science & Network Security

Academic knowledge in Linux, Java, Python, Assembly, C, C#, JavaScript, web programming, PHP, HTML, CSS, Angular, React, Node.Js, Webpack, Spring Boot, SQL and DBMS, Git, technical communications, IT security policies, Cryptography, Computer networks administration, Penetration testing using Kali Linux and network security.

Linnéuniversitetet - Växjö, Sweden 2015 - 2018 Higher Education Diploma in Computer Science

Azad University - Tehran, Iran 2006 - 2009 Association degree in Computer Science

Academic knowledge in Java, C, Pascal, computer networksandfundamental of computer science.

High school of computer science - Tehran, Iran 2003 - 2006

Knowledge in Visual basic, programming andmathematics.

Career Summary

System Developer MegaMiner - Tehran, Iran 2019 - Present

Automation, Designs and create software solutions, Prototyping and modifying code to fix errors, Develop backend, Develop Frontend, Design and build the view, UI, with focus on UX. I am also do research and development for the company and hire new talents.

System Developer Ericsson - Karlskrona, Sweden 2018 - 2019

Telecommunications, Linux, Java, Python, Groovy, Gerrit, Git, CI-CD, Jenkins-dsl, Maven, Gradle, Unit testing, Integration testing, SonarQube, Mantis Issue Tracker, code reviews, vSphere, VMware, AWS, polyth programming, agile DevOps methodology, system and full stack development, REST, Spring Boot and API.

IT Manager STNJ - Tehran, Iran 2011 - 2014

Manage the entire network system and computers. Prepare computers and network as required by the staff and support and fix network issues.

Professional Skills

Coding Languages:

JavaScript, HTML/CSS, Python SQL, Java, Node.js, PHP, Kotlin

Frameworks/Systems:

MVC, AngularJS, bootstrap

E-commerce solutions:

WordPress, Prestashop, Shopify, Plugin developer

Cybersecurity:

Kali, ethical hacking, Strong knowledge in blue and red teams tactics, Strong knowledge in cyber attacks and defense solutions